Smoking causes cancer.
Smoking kills.
Drinking alcohol
is injurious to health.
[Music]
[Background Murugar Song]
Hello… Hello sir…
Sir, can you hear me?
Yes sir… one minute sir…
Just one minute…
Hello sir, tell me sir.
Dheera, there’s nothing more to say.
Your name is already on the layoff list.
You still haven’t completed your target.
If the amount doesn’t come by evening, I’m sorry…
After that, I can’t do anything.
I’ll definitely come with the money and meet you this evening, sir.
Sure?
Sure sir
Ok, Make it fast
People sitting comfortably in AC rooms giving advice don’t know the real pain.
Don't die man
At this rate, I’ll die before finishing collections.
[Bell Rings]
Is this Raghav’s house?
Yes. Who are you?
I’m Dheera. Collection agent.
He asked me to come home for EMI collection. Is he not here?
No, he’s gone out.
Gone out? Who are you?
I’m his friend.
Do you know when he’ll be back?
Half an hour to one hour.
Half an hour… Raghav… Raghav…
He wont pick
Why?
He left his phone at home.
Left it here?
If you’re waiting, come inside and sit, bro.
No bro, I’ll wait outside.
It’s okay bro, come in.
Let’s have coffee. It’s getting late anyway.
Okay, fine.
Looks like he really went out.
Please sit, brother.
Thalapathi, huh?
What bro? Tea or coffee?
Coffee.
hmm
Looks  like a genuinely good person.
[Thalapathy Movie Plays]
Why is this coffee such a strange color?
Is this black coffee?
Coffee or Drinks?
Bro, just coffee. I’ve got work.
Bro, the coffee is good.
Thanks.
Bro, is Raghav a doctor?
No, medical student.
Which college?
Tiruppur Medical College.
You too?
Yes
Bro, I have a doubt.
For many days, I’ve had pain on the left side of my head.
Do you smoke a lot?
Bro, how do you know?
Dark lips. Anyone can tell.
Bro, one small doubt.
Any idea to get rid of headache without quitting cigarettes?
I have an idea.
What bro?
How many cigarettes do you smoke a day?
About five.
Smoke ten a day. The pain will go.
I asked for peaceful sleep, he’s giving me an idea to sleep forever.
Mental Fellow
What?
Nothing bro.
I said once my salary comes, I’ll buy more cigarettes.
Why? Too many cigarettes?
Too much work pressure?
It’s a dog’s life, bro. Running behind people to collect money, life drains out and comes back.
Someone takes compound loan, personal loan, loan after loan.
When we call and ask for EMI,
“This week bro… next week bro… next month bro…”
And when we trust them and go to the bank,
the manager scolds us saying,
“Can’t you even collect money properly?”
Handling all this and reaching target just to get salary…
It becomes unbearable, bro.
Looks like five cigarettes aren’t enough for your suffering.
Five?
Even ten won’t be enough.
[Scene from Thalapathy Movie]
Anyway, he is going to die in the movie
You really like Thalapathi?
Who doesn’t like Thalapathi?
It’s about friendship.
Friendship?
What do you think about friendship?
What?
I asked what you think about friendship.
Why are you suddenly asking?
Just tell me.
Friendship means being happy. Knowing each other’s plus and minus.Like this… making coffee and offering it.
That’s it.
You said plus and minus…
What’s my minus?
I know bro.
Stammering Problem. I adjust
Am I that bad that you have to adjust?
Sorry bro, I didn’t mean it that way.
Don’t misunderstand.
Chill bro. Friends.
Can I call you by your name?
Why not bro? Call me.
Ram
What?
Hey… sounds like drunk and blabbering.
Ram. That’s my name.
Okay Ram.
Did you ever have any ambition?
Ambition?
asked suddenly…
Mm
Yes.
I did, bro.
I wanted to become a big person in archery.
But situations forced me to quit.
Why? No support from family or friends?
Family didn’t support much.
Friends still ask what happened to my ambition.
An archery kit itself costs more than 60,000.
Our desires are always too expensive.
So I gave it up.
Not like you.
I had a small dream. I wanted to become an actor.
Wow. That’s the biggest dream of all.
Okay, listen. Its my big dream okay?
Okay.. Okay..
I worked hard, saved money,
Produced, directed, and acted in a short film myself.
It cost less than your archery kit.
Only 20,000.
Stop joking and tell.
My friend Raghav—
He’s not just my friend, he’s an influencer.
I asked him to promote my short film.
He did.
That’s good. Views must have poured in.
Yes, views came well.
But do you know what he did, Dheera?
What?
Hey Raghav! What nonsense did you do?
What did I do?
I asked you to promote my short film.
Why did you unnecessarily talk about me?
What did I say?
You said I keep pausing while talking.
That’s what audience likes!
If you wanted someone who talks in rhyme,was my problem the only one available? Who gave you rights to insult me?
Why are you overreacting?
I treated you like a friend.  Friend?
With that stammering problem, you talk like this?
If your conversation is so good?
Go fix it first and then talk.
Don’t talk unnecessarily.
Tell me Dheera,
Is it my fault that I was born like this?
Mr. Bean, Hrithik Roshan—
they all had this problem, didn’t they?
They became actors, right?
Why can’t I?
You could’ve punched him at least once, Ram.
After that he wouldn’t talk like this.
Correct, Dheera.
I hit him.
Did you hit him?
He died.
What?
I hit him.
He died.
Looks like he really went *****
Don’t joke, Ram.
I’m leaving. Tell Raghav to call me when he comes.
Sorry, Dheera.Time brought you here.
Time made me come here.
Time made me kill him.
Time made you the scapegoat.
I didn’t expect this.
After he died, I didn’t know what to do.
Then I heard a vehicle stop downstairs.
I went to check who it was.
That’s when I saw you.
I already seen you dheera
when you came to collect EMI earlier.
I guessed you’d come here somehow.
I decided to trap you.
Don’t worry, Dheera. Tomorrow morning when you wake up,
you won’t remember anything that happened here.
You won’t remember my friend.
You won’t remember me either.
You’re scared?
Won’t you do even this much for a friend, Dheera?
Do you know what tomorrow’s news will be?
“A collection agent murdered a person
for failing to repay loan EMI.”
“At the scene of the murder,
the accused collapsed unconscious.”
Perfect, isn’t it?
What acting!
No, Ram.
I have a family.
I also have a family, Dheera.
["Kattukuyilu" Song from Thalapathy]
Bell Rings & Door Knocks
Title: THALAPATHY
Subtitle by HARISH K KRISH